Register of the Atlantic Council of the United States Records, 1950-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1959-1981
  - Alphabetical
    - South Carolina, University of, 1964-65 (Folder 18)
    - Southern California, University of, 1963-67 (Folder 19)
    - Sponsor correspondence, 1964-66 (Folder 20)
    - Stanford Research Institute, 1964-65 (Folder 21)
    - Starr, Chauncey, 1977-78 (Folder 22)
    - State University of New York, 1964-68 (32, Folder 1)
    - Sterling, Richard, 1968 (Folder 2)
    - Stevenson, Adlai III, 1967-1970 (Folder 3)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1963-64 (Folder 4)
    - Steyn, Julian J., 1975-77 (Folder 5)
    - Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, 1975 (Folder 6)
    - Strauss, Robert S., 1977 (Folder 7)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert
      - 1963-64 (Folder 8)
      - 1965-1970 (Folder 9)
      - 1979 (Folder 10)
    - Streit, Clarence, 1962-64 (Folder 11)
    - Sussex, University of, 1965 (Folder 12)
    - Swarthmore College, 1963-65 (Folder 13)
    - T
      - 1962-64 (Folder 14)
      - 1962-68 (Folder 15)
    - Texas, University of, 1963-65 (Folder 16)
    - Tillman, Seth, 1968 (Folder 17)
    - Trade Policy Research Centre, 1973-74 (33, Folder 1)
    - Truitt, Wesley B., 1965 (Folder 2)
    - Tufts University, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1964 (Folder 3)
    - Turkish Group of ATA, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Tyler, John, 1964-65 (Folder 5)
    - U, 1962-68 (Folder 6)
    - U-Z, 1964-68 (Folder 7)
    - UNESCO Conference, October 1963 (Folder 8)
    - Union College (Schenectady, NY), 1965 (Folder 9)
    - U.S. Congress, 1965 (Folder 10)
    - U.S. Department of State
      - 1962-64 (Folder 11)
      - 1965-69 (Folder 12)
      - 1971 (Folder 13)
      - 1973 (Folder 14)
    - U.S. Naval Academy, 1964-66 (Folder 15)
    - V
      - 1962-64 (34, Folder 1)
      - 1963-65 (Folder 2)
    - Vaerno, Grethe, 1976 (Folder 3)
    - Valluy, General, 1963 (Folder 4)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1966-67 (Folder 5)
    - Van Der Valk, J., 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Van Zeeland, Paul, 1964-65 (Folder 7)
    - Vermont, University of, 1963 (Folder 8)
    - Virginia, University of, 1963-64 (Folder 9)
  - Alphabetical
    - W
      - 1962-64 (Folder 10)
      - 1963-68 (Folder 11-12)
      - 1965 (Folder 13)
      - 1965-67 (Folder 14)
    - Wackernagel, Elinore
      - 1962-63 (Folder 15)
      - 1963-66 (Folder 16)
    - Washington, University of, 1963-67 (Folder 17)
    - Watson, Thomas J., 1962-67 (Folder 18)
    - Waugh, Samuel C., 1967-1970 (Folder 19)
    - Werle, Ira C., 1971 (Folder 20)
    - Weseloh, Hans A., 1968 (Folder 21)
    - White House, 1968-1973 (35, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Lynn A., 1962 (Folder 2)
    - Wilson, John R., 1966 (Folder 3)
    - Winthrop, John, 1963-64 (Folder 4)
    - Wisconsin, University of, 1965-67 (Folder 5)
    - Wriston, Walter B., 1967 (Folder 6)
    - Y, 1963-66 (Folder 7)
    - Yardley, Richard Q., 1962 (Folder 8)
    - Young, James, 1963 (Folder 9)
    - Zellerbach, James D., 1962-63 (Folder 10)
    - Zlotnick, Sidney, 1963 (Folder 11)
    - Zolotas, Xenophon, 1967 (Folder 12)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1950-1985
  - Abel, I. W., testimony before the House Ways and Means Committee, May 17, 1973 (35, Folder 13)
  - Abs, Hermann J., n.d. (Folder 14)
  - Abt, Clark C.
    - "Arms Control and Disarmament," (Folder 15)
    - "Nuclear Diffusion to the Allies,", n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Academic Clearing House Study Project, February 1, 1970 (Folder 17)
  - Acheson, Dean, "Europe: Kaleidoscope or Clouded Crystal,", March 13, 1963 (Folder 18)
  - Accounting and legal expenses
    - 1962-63 (Folder 19)
    - 1963 (Folder 20)
    - 1964-69 (Folder 21)
  - Achilles, Theodore C.
    - 1965-66 (Folder 22)
    - 1967-68 (Folder 23-24)
    - 1967-1970 (36, Folder 1)
    - 1971-73 (Folder 2)
    - 1972 (Folder 3)
    - 1972-74 (Folder 4)
    - 1973 (Folder 5)
    - 1980 (Folder 6)
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Atlantic Institute, 1980-81 (Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors, 1976-78 (Folder 9)
    - Clippings (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence
      - 1962 (Folder 11)
      - 1963 (Folder 12)
      - 1964 (Folder 13)
      - 1967-69 (Folder 14)
      - 1971-72 (37, Folder 1)
      - 1972 January-December (Folder 2)
      - 1973
        - January-June (Folder 3)
        - September-December (Folder 4)
      - 1973-77 (Folder 5)
      - 1974
        - January-December (Folder 6-7)
        - April-June (Folder 8)
        - various months (Folder 9)
      - 1974-77 (Folder 10)
      - 1975
        - January-March (38, Folder 1)
        - January-May (Folder 2)
        - January-June (Folder 3)
        - February-December (Folder 4)
        - April-June (Folder 5)
        - June-December (Folder 6)
      - 1975-76 (Folder 7)
      - 1976
        - January-April (Folder 8)
        - January-June (Folder 9)
        - May-August (Folder 10)
        - July-December (Folder 11)
        - September-December (39, Folder 1)
      - 1977
        - January-June (Folder 2)
        - June-December (Folder 3)
      - 1978
        - January-April (Folder 4)
        - September-December (Folder 5)
        - various months (Folder 6)
      - 1979
        - January-March (Folder 7)
        - April-July (Folder 8)
        - various months (Folder 9)
      - 1980 (40, Folder 1)
      - 1980-81 (Folder 2)
      - 1981 (Folder 3-4)
      - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs
        - 1976-77 (Folder 5)
        - 1979 (Folder 6)
      - Atlantic Treaty Association, 1978-79 (Folder 7)
      - Center for International Security Studies, 1978-79 (Folder 8)
      - Commission on US-Brazilian Relations, 1979 (Folder 9)
      - E, 1978-79 (Folder 10)
      - Eastman Kodak Company, 1967-68 (Folder 11)
      - F, 1978-79 (41, Folder 1)
      - Federal Union, 1979-1981 (Folder 2)
      - Fraternite d'Armes France-Etats-Unis, 1974-79 (Folder 3)
      - International Management and Development In- stitute, 1979 (Folder 4-5)
      - Merchant, Livingston T., 1967-68 (Folder 5A)
      - N
        - 1974-79 (Folder 6)
        - 1979-1981 (Folder 7)
      - NATO, 1979 (Folder 8)
      - New Leadership Fund, 1977-79 (42, Folder 1)
      - Rostow, Eugene, 1977 (Folder 2)
      - S, 1976-79 (Folder 3)
      - School of Advanced, 1968 (Folder 4)
      - Stanford University, 1979 (Folder 5)
      - U.S. Information Agency, 1974 (Folder 5A)
      - York University, 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Treaty Association (Folder 7)
    - Committee on Present Danger (Folder 8)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Folder 9)
    - Federal Union (Folder 10)
    - Food Project, 1978 (Folder 11)
    - Fundraising (Folder 12)
    - Gray Area (Folder 13)
    - Greece and Turkey (Folder 14)
    - Hamburg, September 20-23, 1978 (Folder 15)
    - Harmel report, 1967 (Folder 16)
    - "Himalayan Wedding,", n.d. (Folder 17)
    - International Democratic Community (Folder 18)
    - Medicare (43, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, 1968 (Folder 2)
    - Middle East Working Group (Folder 3)
    - Political Committee, 1978 (Folder 4)
    - Political Working Groups
      - I (Folder 5)
      - III (Folder 6)
    - St. John's Vestry, 1973-76 (Folder 7)
    - "Toward Better Management of Interdependence," Febru- ary, 1978 (Folder 8)
  - Action Committee for the United States of Europe (Folder 9)
  - Action Program and Summary Statement (Folder 10)
  - Activities Reports
    - 1967 September (Folder 11)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 12)
  - Ad Hoc Executive Committee (Folder 13)
  - Adams, John (Folder 14)
  - Advertising Council
    - 1963-65 (Folder 15)
    - 1967-78 (Folder 16)
    - Campaign, 1968-69
      - General (Folder 17)
      - Criticism of campaign re: grammar (Folder 18)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company
        - Correspondence, April 1968-July 1969 (44, Folder 1)
        - Direct mail stamp proposal (Folder 2)
        - Merchant, Livingston T., letter, April 16, 1969 (Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 4)
      - Replies to campaign
        - Magazines (Folder 5)
        - Newspapers (Folder 6)
        - Radio and television (Folder 7-8)
        - Sports Illustrated (Folder 9)
      - Requests for information about Atlantic Council
        - 1969
          - June-July (Folder 10-11)
          - July-August (45, Folder 1-2)
          - August (Folder 3-4)
          - August-September (Folder 5)
          - September-October (Folder 6-8)
          - November-December (46, Folder 1)
        - 1970 January-April (Folder 2)
      - 20th Anniversary Committee (Folder 3)
    - 1969 (Folder 4-6)
    - 1969 (47, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, 1971-74
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-72 (Folder 2)
        - 1972-73 (Folder 3)
        - Receipts, invoices, 1972-74 (Folder 4)
        - Reports, bulletins, 1971-73 (Folder 5)
        - Requests for media coverage, 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Advisory Trade Panel
    - 1978 (Folder 7)
    - 1979-1980 (Folder 8)
    - 1980-81 (47A, Folder 1)
  - Agger, Donald G., "Economies Obtainable From Common Defense Production," (Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1967-1971 (Folder 3)
  - "Agriculture and the Quality of Life,", 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Agriculture study
    - 1971-73 (Folder 5)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1971-74
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Abel, Martin (Folder 8)
      - Andrew Mellon Foundation (Folder 9)
      - Bank of America (Folder 10)
      - Barter, P.G.H. (Folder 11)
      - Battelle Memorial Institute (Folder 12)
      - Caldwell, Harry B. (Folder 13)
      - Cargill Foundation (Folder 14)
      - Cochrane, Willard (Folder 15)
      - Corbet, Hugh (Folder 16)
      - D'Ansembourg, Charles F. (Folder 17)
      - First Interoceanic Corporation (Folder 18)
      - Ford Foundation (Folder 19)
      - Frederick, Robert M. (Folder 20)
      - Geiger, Theodore (48, Folder 1)
      - George J. Giannini Foundation (Folder 2)
      - Harberger, Arnold (Folder 3)
      - Hedges, Irwin (Folder 4)
      - Herlitska, Andre (Folder 5)
      - Hillman, Jimmye (Folder 6)
      - Johnson, Gale (Folder 7)
      - Johnson Foundation (Folder 8)
      - Joslin, Tim (Folder 9)
      - Kirk, David (Folder 10)
      - Knottnerus, C.S. (Folder 11)
      - Lucq, Jean-Marc (Folder 12)
      - Malgrem, Harald (Folder 13)
      - Malve, Pierre (Folder 14)
      - Marsh, John (Folder 15)
      - Miyawaki, Asao (Folder 16)
      - Naden, Kenneth (Folder 17)
      - Patton, James C. (Folder 18)
      - Petit, Michel (Folder 19)
      - Praeger Publishers (Folder 20)
      - Priebe, Hermann (Folder 21)
      - Richard King Mellon Charitable Trusts (Folder 22)
      - Rockefeller Foundation (Folder 23)
      - Ruttan, Vernon (Folder 24)
      - Savary, Roger (Folder 25)
      - Schnittker, John A. (Folder 26)
      - Scott, John (The National Grange) (Folder 27)
      - Simantov, Andre (Folder 28)
      - Soth, Lawrence (Folder 29)
      - Straus, Ralph (Folder 30)
      - Tuthill, John W. (Folder 31)
      - United Brand Company (Folder 32)
      - Warley, T. K. (Folder 33)
      - Winegarten, Asher (Folder 34)
      - Yates, Lamartine (Folder 35)
    - Financial arrangements (Folder 36)
    - Foundations (Folder 37)
    - Memoranda (Folder 38)
    - Project reviewers (49, Folder 1)
    - Research materials
      - Background papers and reports (Folder 2)
      - Papers by various authors (Folder 3)
    - Steering Committee (Folder 4)
    - Subject file
      - Biographical notes on authors (Folder 5)
      - Form letters and printing services (Folder 6)
      - Foundation descriptions (Folder 7)
      - Master list of recipients of published report (Folder 8)
      - Miscellany (Folder 9)
      - Press conference, July 1973 (Folder 10)
      - Receipts, clippings, requests for published reports (Folder 11)
      - Steering Committee
        - Memoranda (Folder 12)
        - Meetings, 1972
          - May 27-28 (50, Folder 1)
          - September 29-30 (Folder 2)
          - December 15-16 (Folder 3)
      - "U.S. Agriculture in a World Context"
        - Comments by reviewers (Folder 4)
        - December drafts (Folder 5-6)
        - Drafts, 1-12 (Folder 7-8)
        - Final comments and conclusions (Folder 9)
        - Final drafts (51, Folder 1)
  - Ailleret, General, "Defense in All Directions," n.d (Folder 2)
  - Airlie House Conference, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - "Allied Command, Europe, Its Strategy, Its Forces," briefing, March 12, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - American Association of Collegiate Schools of Business and International University Contact for Management Education (Folder 5)
  - American Committee for Responsible Democratic Government in Greece (Folder 6)
  - American Council of Young Political Leaders
    - 1963 (Folder 7)
    - 1964 (Folder 8)
    - 1965 (Folder 9)
    - 1966 (Folder 10)
    - 1967 (Folder 11)
    - 1968-69 (52, Folder 1)
    - 1970 (Folder 2)
    - 1971 (Folder 3)
    - General (Folder 4)
    - German delegation visit, October 24-November 7, 1968 (Folder 5-6)
  - American Ditchley Foundation (Folder 7)
  - American Foreign Service Association (Folder 8-9)
  - American Institute for Foreign Trade (Folder 10)
  - American Nuclear Society Conference, 1980 (Folder 11)
  - American Nuclear Society Conference, 1980 (53, Folder 1-2)
  - American subsidiaries of foreign direct investors in the U.S. (Folder 3)
  - American Surveys, 1962-63 (Folder 4)
  - American Veterans Committee, resolution, May 21, 1961 (Folder 5)
  - Americans for Winning the Peace (Folder 6-7)
  - Amsterdam follow-up, 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Clay, "Policymaking in the First Half-Century of the Federal Reserve System,", 1965 (Folder 9)
  - Anonymous gift, 1974 (Folder 10)
  - Aron, Raymond, "From Independence to Neutrality,", February 22, 1968 (Folder 11)
  - Asia Society, 1971 (Folder 12)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Folder 13)
  - Association Francaise pour la Communaute Atlantique (Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Action Committee
    - 1966 May-December (54, Folder 1-2)
    - 1967 January-June (Folder 3)
    - General (Folder 4-5)
  - Atlantic alliance, French and German polls, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Assembly Committee, 1963-67 (Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Business Survey, 1962 (Folder 8)
  - Atlantic College
    - 1964 (Folder 9)
    - 1965 (Folder 10)
    - Applications, 1967 (55, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - Ceperley, David, 1966-67 (Folder 2)
      - Milstein, Robert, 1966-67 (Folder 3)
    - Scholarship requests, 1966 (Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Colleges (Folder 5)
  - "The Atlantic Community," introduction (Folder 6)
  - "The Atlantic Community and Southeast Asia,", December 1965 (Folder 7)
  - "Atlantic Community - Bridge to Peace?", conference, University of Texas, February 12, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Community Conference, third annual, April 26-27, 1968 (Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Community Educational Program, 1980 (Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Community News
    - 1964 (Folder 10A)
    - 1970 February (Folder 11)
    - 1973 February (Folder 12)
    - 1974
      - November (Folder 13)
      - December (Folder 14)
    - 1975
      - January (Folder 15)
      - February (56, Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April-May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August-September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (57, Folder 1)
      - Special edition (Folder 2)
    - 1976
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February (Folder 4)
      - March (Folder 5)
      - April (Folder 6)
      - May (Folder 7)
      - June (Folder 8)
      - July-August (58, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1977
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (Folder 8)
      - April (59, Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July-August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
      - November (Folder 7)
      - December (Folder 8)
    - 1978
      - January (60, Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June-July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Folder 8)
      - October (61, Folder 1)
      - November (Folder 2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1979
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May (62, Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July-August (Folder 3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - Bills, 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Community Quarterly
    - 1964-65 (Folder 8)
    - 1965-67 (Folder 9)
    - 1968 (Folder 10)
    - 1968 (63, Folder 1)
    - 1969
      - Winter (Folder 2-3)
      - various months (Folder 4-5)
    - 1970
      - Fall (Folder 6)
      - Winter (Folder 7)
      - various months (Folder 8)
    - 1971
      - Spring (Folder 9)
      - Fall (Folder 10)
    - 1971-72 (64, Folder 1-2)
    - 1972
      - Summer (Folder 3)
      - Winter (Folder 4)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 5-6)
    - 1973-74 (Folder 7)
    - 1974 (Folder 8-9)
    - 1975-76 (65, Folder 1-2)
    - 1977 (Folder 3)
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Achilles, Theodore C., gifts of (Folder 5)
    - Address changes (Folder 6)
    - Advertising
      - 1962-65 (Folder 7)
      - 1966-67 (Folder 8)
    - Airlines and ship companies, 1964 (Folder 9)
    - Atlantic biography (Folder 10)
    - Bills
      - 1967 (Folder 11)
      - 1968 (Folder 12)
      - 1969 (Folder 13)
      - 1969-1970 (66, Folder 1)
      - 1971-72 (Folder 2)
      - Advance receipts, 1969 (Folder 3)
      - Bert Garmise Associates, Inc., 1969 (Folder 4)
      - Globe Mail Agency, Inc., 1969 (Folder 5)
      - Monumental Publishing Company, 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Christmas effort, 1966 (Folder 7)
    - Circulation build-up, 1964-67 (Folder 8)
    - Complaints (Folder 9)
    - Conference, October 5, 1963 (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence
      - 1963-69 (Folder 11)
      - 1967-68 (Folder 12)
      - 1970-72 (Folder 13)
      - 1973-75 (Folder 14)
      - Goodman, Elliott, 1965-68 (Folder 15)
      - Letters to the editor, 1964-68 (Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous (67, Folder 1)
    - D. C. Heath and Company
      - 1972-74 (Folder 2)
      - 1974-76 (Folder 3)
    - Donors, mailings to, 1964-65 (Folder 4)
    - European-Atlantic Movement (Folder 5)
    - Exchange subscriptions
      - 1963-65 (Folder 6)
      - 1964-68 (Folder 7)
    - Expenses, 1963 (68, Folder 1)
    - French translation, 1963-66 (Folder 2)
    - Garmise Drive, 1967-68 (Folder 3)
    - Materials considered, but not used, 1971-73 (Folder 4-5)
    - Materials rejected
      - 1969 (Folder 6)
      - 1970 (Folder 7-8)
    - Permissions for reprints
      - 1964 (69, Folder 1)
      - 1964-69 (Folder 2)
      - 1965 (Folder 3)
      - 1966 (Folder 4)
      - 1967 (Folder 5)
      - 1968 (Folder 6)
      - 1969
        - Spring (70, Folder 1)
        - Summer (Folder 2)
        - Fall (Folder 3)
        - Winter (Folder 4)
        - various months (Folder 5)
      - 1970
        - Spring (Folder 6)
        - Summer (Folder 7)
    - Renewals, 1964-69 (Folder 8)
    - Subscription refunds
      - 1967-68 (Folder 9)
      - 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Convention, 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Convention of NATO Nations, Paris, January 8-20, 1962
    - General (Folder 12-13)
    - General (71, Folder 1)
    - Addresses, speeches, remarks (Folder 2)
    - Committee No. II, resolutions and recommendations (Folder 3)
    - Congressional Record (Folder 4)
    - Declaration of Paris (Folder 5)
    - Draft report to Congress (Folder 6)
    - Freedom and Union, 1959-1962 (Folder 7)
    - Hallstein, Walter, United Europe - Challenge and Opportunity, excerpts from (Folder 8)
    - International Preparatory Committee (Folder 9)
    - Letters of transmittal (Folder 10)
    - Letters sent to selected members of U.S. Congress (Folder 11)
    - NATO countries embassy libraries in Washington, D.C. (Folder 12)
    - NATO parliamentarians recommendation, November 17, 1961 (Folder 13)
    - P & E Committee (Folder 14)
    - Press (Folder 15)
    - Publicity (72, Folder 1)
    - Resolutions (Folder 2)
    - Subcommittee meetings (Folder 3)
    - Summary reports (Folder 4)
    - Wallace report (Folder 5)
  - "Atlantic Cooperation and Economic Growth,", May/June 1966 (Folder 6)
  - "Atlantic Cooperation in Science and Technology,", 11/66 (Folder 7)
  - "Atlantic Council - What Is It?" (Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Council of Canada (Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Council Report, European-American Business Climate, Foreword, August 8, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - "Atlantic Financial Issues,", November 1966 (Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Free Trade Area (Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Information Center for Teachers
    - 1965-68 (Folder 13)
    - 1969-1970 (Folder 14)
    - 1971 (Folder 15)
    - 1972-73 (73, Folder 1)
    - 1974 (Folder 2)
    - Conference, October 17-19, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Institute
    - 1968 (Folder 4)
    - 1970 (Folder 5)
    - Director General Nominating Committee, 1963 (Folder 6)
    - Fund raising, 1966-67 (Folder 7)
    - Loans, 1964 (Folder 8)
    - Paris (Folder 9)
    - Publications list (Folder 10)
    - Transfer of funds, 1963 (Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Report, 1972 (Folder 13)
  - "Atlantic News,", 1967-68 (Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Papers, sales and promotion, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Atlantic School of Business Administration in Europe (74, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic studies at the secondary level (Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Studies bibliography
    - Correspondence (Folder 3)
    - Distribution (Folder 4)
    - Library of Congress ordering cards (Folder 5)
    - List of texts (Neumann Project) (Folder 6)
  - "The Atlantic System in the 70s" (Folder 7-8)
  - Atlantic trade study (British) (Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Union award dinner, June 11, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Union Committee, 1951-52 (Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Union Committee, Inc., 1961-63 (Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Union resolutions, 1969-1971 (Folder 13)
  - Australia and nuclear energy (75, Folder 1)
  - "Avoiding War and Controlling Arms Toward the Year 2000,", July 26, 1984 (Folder 2)
  - Ball, George W., address before the 48th National Foreign Trade Convention, NYC, November 1, 1961 (Folder 3)
  - Bank deposits
    - 1962 (Folder 4)
    - 1963 (Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - 1971 (Folder 7)
  - Bank statements
    - 1962-63 (Folder 8)
    - 1963 (Folder 9)
    - 1968 (Folder 10)
  - Barret Group (Folder 11)
  - Batt Bates & Company, 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Battelle Memorial Institute (Folder 13-14)
  - Battelle Memorial Institute (76, Folder 1)
  - Battelle seminar and study programs, 1977 (Folder 2)
  - Beer, Francis A. (Folder 3)
  - Belgian resolution, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Belgian-US industrial cooperation (Folder 5)
  - "Better Means for Reaching Agreement,", 1966 (Folder 6)
  - "Beyond Diplomacy,", 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Bibliographical service, December 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Bibliographies (Folder 9-10)
  - Bills
    - 1963 (77, Folder 1)
    - 1964 (Folder 2)
    - 1968 (Folder 3)
    - 1969 (Folder 4)
    - 1969-1970 (Folder 5)
    - 1970
      - January-February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April (Folder 8)
      - May (78, Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
      - November (79, Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
      - various months (Folder 3)
    - 1971
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (80, Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April-May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - August-September (81, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - November-December (Folder 4)
    - 1972
      - January-February (Folder 5)
      - March (82, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)